https://lacrossesa.com.au/privacy-statement/

www.lacrossesa.com.au
Lacrosse South Australia Inc maintains a policy of strict confidence concerning your personal information and work to ensure that this website is compliant with the relevant Privacy legislation in Australia and South Australia including but not limited to the Privacy Act 1988.
Access to this website (www.lacrossesa.com.au) is conditional on your acceptance of the terms of this Privacy Statement.
Personal information
Any information you choose to provide to us will be collected to for the purpose of enhancing your use of the Site, to improve the Site, and to keep you informed of relevant upcoming events and activities.
Use and disclosure of information
We will never disclose information that personally identifies you to any third party other than as set out in this Privacy Statement.
Cookies
When you visit the Site the server may attach a “cookie” to your computer’s memory. A “cookie” assists us to store information on how visitors to the Site use it and the pages that may be of most interest. This information is not linked to any personal information you may provide and cannot be used to identify you.
You can adjust your browser settings so that it disables “cookies” or does not accept them if you wish to do so.
Third Parties and your information
We will only collect, store, use or disseminate information that personally identifies you as set out in this Privacy Statement unless we are required to protect our rights or property (or those of any third party), or to avoid injury to any person, by law.
Although the Site may link directly to websites operated by third parties you acknowledge that third party sites are not operated by us. We encourage you to always read the applicable privacy statement of any linked third party site.
Your consent
By your use of the website you consent to the collection, storage, use and dissemination of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Statement and as otherwise permitted under the Privacy Act.
Storage and security
We will use all reasonable endeavours to keep your personal information in a secure environment. These measures are designed to assist in your personal information not being accessed by unauthorised personnel, lost or misused. If you believe that there has been unauthorised use or disclosure of your personal information please contact us (see below).
Variation
We may at any time vary the terms of this Privacy Statement. You should check this Privacy Statement regularly so that you are aware of any variations made to this Privacy Statement. You will be deemed to have consented to such variations by your continued use of the Site following such changes being made.
Contact Us
If you wish to access your personal information, you believe your privacy has been breached or would like to update your details, please contact us:
Got a Question? Contact us with your question here or feedback via email.
@2017 Lacrosse South Australia. All rights reserved.
